A Guide to the Richard Corbin Papers, 1746-1825
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
- Receipted account of John Lyne with Russell & Temple, 30 June 1798. (Box-folder 2:5)
- Receipted account of John Lyne with Thomas Hooper, 30 June 1798. (Box-folder 2:5)
- Receipted account of Richard Corbin with Thomas Jeffries, July 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Thomas Martin to Richard Corbin, 13 July 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Hannah Bray to Richard Corbin, 14 July 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipted account of Corbin with John Didley, 25 July 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Hacket & Grant, 16 August 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipted account of Corbin with James Guy, 24 August 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Richard Bowden, 24 August 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Account of Richard Corbin to Benjamin Pendleton, 10 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Onslow Wakeford to Richard Corbin, 13 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Robert Bowden to Richard Corbin, 14 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Thomas Fauntleroy to Richard Corbin, 17 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Richard Moore to Tholley Wood for Richard Corbin, 18 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Order, Thomas Jeffries on Richard Corbin, receipted, 22 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt from Richard Ball to Richard Corbin, 24 September 1798. (Box-folder 2:6)
- Receipt, John Hoones, 2 October 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Account of Richard Corbin with Byrd Beverley, 8 October 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipt from Beverley Cloudas, 25 October 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipt from Thomas Trice, 25 October 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Account of Corbin with John Henderson, 16 November 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Richard Frazier, 7 December 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Bond. Richard Corbin to Charles Carter trustee of William Byrd, 29 December 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Wythe and Langley, 31 December 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Monsieur Richard Corbin with Lewis Wercy, 31 December 1798. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with George Garrett, 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Corn made at Moss Neck, 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Order. Richard Corbin on Francis Corbin, 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Account of Corbin with Thomas Goodwin, 9 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Wercy, 12 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with John McBride, 17 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Benjamin Stetson, 18 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- James Brown's receipt for tobacco, 21 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipt from W. Lyne, 22 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Augustine Davis, 23 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with William Mewburn, 23 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipt from Robert Cockburn, 25 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Liston Temple, 26 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Richard Corbin with Wercy, 26 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Jacob Harrison, 26 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Alexander Shackleford, 28 January 1799. (Box-folder 2:7)
- Receipt of Edward Garrett to Richard Corbin, 5 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt of Edward Garrett to Richard Corbin, 6 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Matthew Glenn, 13 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Order from James Trice on Richard Corbin, receipted 17 February, 16 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Order from John Adams on Richard Corbin, 19 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Samuel Chiles, 19 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt from John Moore, Jr., to Richard Corbin, 24 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Order, James Trice on Richard Corbin, 25 February 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Thomas Strachan, 31 March 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Bond and receipt, James Wilson, 11 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of the treasury of the Piankatank Canal Company to Robert Smith, 19 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt to Benjamin Moore, 21 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt to Thomas Metcalf, 21 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt to Richard Corbin, 21 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Hugh Ropley, 22 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Benjamin Seward, 23 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Account of Corbin with John Shackelford, 24 April 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipted account of Corbin with R. Coltart, 8 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:8)
- Receipt from James Jones to Richard Corbin, 10 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Order, from James Trice on Richard Corbin, receipted, 10 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipt from John Didlake to Richard Corbin, 10 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipt from James Lupkin to Richard Corbin, 14 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with T. Garnett, 15 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Royal R. Allen, 16 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Order, receipted 21 May, from Hazelwood Farrish on Daniel Turner, 13 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Michael Dixon, 21 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipt from Samuel Chiles to Richard Corbin, 28 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Benjamin Waldon, 28 May 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with George, 3 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Order from George Turner on Richard Corbin, receipted, 6 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Account of Corbin with Hazelwood Farrish, 6 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Account of Richard Corbin with Robert Greenhow, 7 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Account of Richard Corbin with Leroy Anderson, 9 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Order, receipted 8 October, Henry Hoffman on Richard Corbin, 17 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Receipted account of Corbin with J. P. Bristow, 30 June 1799. (Box-folder 2:9)
- Account of Corbin with James Ross & Co., 1 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from Charles Willett to Richard Corbin, 9 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipted account with John Southgate, 9 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Account of Corbin with Randolph & Armistead, 10 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Account with Daniel Stane & Co., 12 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Alex Wilson & Co., 12 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Andrew Leckie, 13 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipted account with George Garrett, 18 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from James Hooper to Richard Corbin, 20 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from Tholley M. Wood to Richard Corbin, 20 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from Michael Dixon to Richard Corbin, 26 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Charles Blackey, 27 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from Tholley M. Wood to Richard Corbin, 29 July 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Account of Corbin with Richard & Shackelford, 4 August 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from William Waldon, 8 August 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from B. Mattox to Richard Corbin, 23 August 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Account of Corbin with the Planketank Canal Company, 29 August 1799. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Receipt from Thomas Faunteleroy to Richard Corbin, 5 September 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Receipted account of Corbin with William H. Shackelford, 19 October 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Copy of judgement, Corbin V. Beeman, November 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Receipt, Samuel Shipley, 14 November 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Receipt from William Halyard to Richard Corbin, 26 November 1799. (Folder 2:11)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Samuel Chiles, 10 December 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Account of Corbin with Thomas Goodwin, 12 December 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Lewis Wercq, 17 December 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Order, Thomas Trice on Richard Corbin, receipted, 23 December 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Alexander Shackelford, 23 December 1799. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Account of Gawen Lane Corbin with Richard Corbin, 1 January 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Account of Richard Corbin with Richard Shackelford, 19 April 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Account of John T. Corbin with Warren Ashley, 24 May 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Copy of decree & receipt Gales administrator V. Corbin, 3 June 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- 3 receipts from John Seager, 1800., Printed form with manuscript insertions. (Box-folder 2:11)
- John Browne, St. Johns, Cutting to Richard Corbin 25 October 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Account of Richard Corbin with William Butler, 15 November 1800. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Order, receipted 4 February 1801, Benjamin Hale on Richard Corbin, 19 January 1801. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Receipt, William Segar, 18 August 1801. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Account of Corbin with Thomas Strachan, 6 November 1801. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Samuel Blake & the sheriff of Middlesex County, 25 January 1802. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Deed of release Benjamin Pollard to Richard Corbin for land in Gloucester, 2 February 1802. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Account of Trust estate, James Parke Farley with Alex & Frances Willcox, 12 October 1802. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Account of Richard Corbin with Thomas Montague, 31 December 1803. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fish account, 1805. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fee bill, Middlesex County, August 1805. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Receipted account of Corbin with John T. Willford, 27 May 1806. (Box-folder 2:12)
- N. Robinson, Norfolk, to Richard Corbin, Laneville, 29 May 1810. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Charles S. Henery, Williamsburg, to Richard Corbin, 10 March 1812. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Receipted account of Corbin with Richard T. Shackelford, 25 June 1812. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fee bill, King & Queen County, 1814. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fee bill, Williamsburg, 1814. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fee bill, King & Queen County, 1815. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Fee bill, Williamsburg, 1815. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Thomas Taylor, Richmond, to Richard Corbin, Laneville, 11 December 1816. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Receipted account of Corbin with George Lang, 20 May 1817. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Check to Charles Carter, 20 February 1818. (Box-folder 2:12)
- List of the professors and students of the University of Virginia, [1825] (Box-folder 2:12)
- Alphabet index for ledger B, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Denledy account, George Denledy, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Christopher Daniel to Mr. Corbin, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Dandridge, receipt from Barnes Dandridge to George D. Poindexter, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Plat of unidentified area, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Memo, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Receipted account with T. Evans, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Memo, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Tobacco Book, 1746-1788. (Box 3)
- Letterbook, 1758-1768. (Box 3)
- Diary, 1773-1776. (Box 3)
- Deed of settlement, Griffin to Corbin, 10 December 1778. (Oversize Oversize)